This video is not
sponsors friends in this video I will
tell you how you can download vehicle insurance certificate from Looker.
If
you like our video then
please like and share the video. So let's get started
[music] Open Looker and
log in to it.
Upon logging in to the app, you will get an
interface like this. This is its home page. Here
you will see an option of Issued
Documents. Your issued documents are shown in it.
All the documents that you have already added are shown in it. The
vehicle insurance certificate that we are going to
add here will also be shown
in Issued Documents.
To download vehicle insurance, you
can either click on Explore More here
or there is a search option given below,
click on it. A page like this will appear in front of you.
Here also you will get a search option. Either
you will search by typing insurance in it and then
under it, under the Ministry of Road
Transport, the option of Vehicle Insurance
Certificate will be searched and will appear.
Click on it or you can
scroll down the page a little and here
you will find  You will find the category section. In this, there is an
option of Transport and Infrastructure. Click on it.
After this, click on Ministry of Road Transport and
Highways. Here
you will get the option of Vehicle Insurance Certificate.
Click on it. Now
enter the vehicle details here. You have to
enter your name as it is in your Aadhar
card and vehicle insurance policy.
After this,
enter the vehicle registration number.
How to enter the number is
shown in the example below. After this,
enter son of or wife of or daughter of. If you are a male, then enter son of
or if you are a married woman, then
enter wife of and if you are an unmarried female,
then enter daughter of.
Enter the vehicle's chassis number. You
can see the chassis number from the vehicle's RC and keep this
checkbox ticked as it is
and after this, click on Get Document.
After this, the vehicle's
insurance will start fetching and
in a short while, the vehicle insurance will be
saved in the issue document as you
can see.  The vehicle's insurance
certificate has been added here. Now, if you
want to view or download the vehicle insurance certificate, you need to
click on the three dots next to it.
Here, you'll find a few options. You can view the
vehicle insurance by clicking on View PDF.
Your vehicle insurance will
open. The vehicle number is
written at the top. Below it, the insurance policy
number, the insurance valid date, and the insurance
company's name. After this, your name and address are
written. All these details are written. There's a download
option here. As soon as you click on it, the
vehicle insurance will download.
After this, you can take a printout and
keep it. You can share the
insurance certificate with anyone by clicking here.
If you want to
delete the insurance certificate from the issue document,
you need to click on the three dots.
Here, you'll
find the delete option. You can delete it by clicking on it.
Friends, now you've learned how to
download the vehicle insurance certificate from Looker. That's all
in this video.
If you liked the video, please like,
share, and if you haven't subscribed to our channel yet,  Please
subscribe
and click on the bell icon
so that you can be the
first to receive notifications of our upcoming new videos.
Thanks for watching this
video.